[
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "What is the purpose of the track tag, and when should it be used?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The track tag is used for specifying subtitles. It is typically applied as a child of the audio and video tags.",
      "The track tag is used for specifying subtitles. It is typically applied as a child of the video tag.",
      "The track tag is used for specifying subtitles, captions, and other types of time-based text. It is typically applied as a child of the video tag."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The track tag is used for specifying subtitles, captions, and other types of time-based text. It is typically applied as a child of the audio and video tag."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "When is the link tag used?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "when linking style sheets, JavaScript, and icons for mobile apps",
      "when linking style sheets, favicons, and preloading assets",
      "when linking style sheets, external URLs, and favicons"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "when linking style sheets and favicons"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "The value attribute is associated with which set of tags?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "button,input,form",
      "input,label,meter",
      "input,option,textarea"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "li,input,option"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "When should you use the aside element?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "for anything you want to move to the side, like a pull quote box, a sidebar, or an image with text wrapping around it",
      "for anything in parentheses",
      "for anything in a sidebar"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "when the content can be removed without detracting from the pages message"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "With which tags is the source element associated?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "svg, picture, audio, and video",
      "It is interchangeable with the src attribute, so any element which uses src may use source",
      "audio and video"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "picture, audio, and video"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "When should you use ol and ul elements?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Use ul when you have a list of items in which the order of the items matters. Use ol when you have a list of items that could go in any order.",
      "Use ol when you want a bulleted list and ul when you want a numbered list.",
      "Use ol when you have a list of items in which the order of the items matters. Use ul when you have a list of items that could go in any order."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Use ul when you want a bulleted list and ol when you want a numbered list."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "What is the difference between the div and span tags?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "div is used for major divisions on a page, while span is used to span across columns.",
      "div is the industry-standard default tag, but you could use span if you prefer.",
      "div is used where a generic inline tag is needed, while span is used where a generic block-level tag is needed."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "div is used where a generic block-level tag is needed, while span is used where a generic inline tag is needed."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "What is the hr tag typically used for?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "This tag is depreciated and should not be used.",
      "It draws a horizontal line.",
      "It designates a shift of topic at the section level."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "It designates a topic shift within a section at the paragraph level."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "To get a link to open in a new window or tab",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "_self",
      "_new",
      "_parent"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "_blank"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": " What does the poster attribute do in the video tag?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "It specifies an image that only displays if there is a problem with the video.",
      "It specifies an image that should display until the video is played.",
      "It specifies an image that should display while the video downloads."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "It specifies an image that should display while the video downloads and until the video is played."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "What is the primary purpose of the canvas tag?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "It allows raster images to be rendered on the webpage.",
      "It displays annotated images.",
      "It allows vector images to be rendered on the webpage."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "It allows drawing on a bitmap via JavaScript."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "Which choice contains three valid block-level elements?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "details, abbr, figcaption",
      "canvas, select, noscript",
      "kbd, p, main"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "dt, table, pre"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "Which image formats can be displayed by all web browsers?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "JPG, GIF, TIF",
      "JPG, TIF, BMP",
      " TIF, BMP, GIF"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "PNG, GIF, JPG"
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "You want to have single spacing in between some lines, like in a poem or an address. Which approach should you use?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wrap the text in a box that is the right width so everything wraps correctly. Set the box width with CSS.",
      " Use the pre tag to make the line spacing look exactly like you want.",
      "Separate the lines with the br tag."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Separate lines with a p, then use CSS to make single spacing."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "What does the wbr tag do?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "It requires the browser to wrap the current line at that point.",
      "It breaks a word into two pieces, using a hyphen to connect the words.",
      "It formats a sentence to be easily breakable."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "It presents an opportunity for a break in a very long word, if needed for proper page display."
  },
  {
    "questionType": "HTML",
    "question": "Which statement is false?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Inline elements can be nested inside inline elements.",
      "Block elements can be nested inside block elements.",
      "Inline elements can be nested inside block elements."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Block elements can be nested inside inline elements."
  }
]